<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web development on Diego Sánchez Portfolio</title><link>https://diegosanchezp.github.io/categories/web-development/</link><description>Recent content in Web development on Diego Sánchez Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Everything is mine bro</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 12:27:59 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://diegosanchezp.github.io/categories/web-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Binary theme switcher component</title><link>https://diegosanchezp.github.io/blog/theme-switcher-component/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 12:27:59 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://diegosanchezp.github.io/blog/theme-switcher-component/</guid><description>Introduction A lot of websites nowadays have this feature of having two color schemes for the user to choose, namely &amp;ldquo;dark&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;light&amp;rdquo;, implementing this is a peace of cake with the help of CSS custom properties (variables) and a bit of ECMAscript. Today I present you a web component that abstracts the ECMAscript part and lets you switch between the themes dynamically.
Using the component is straightforward. The component adds and updates a data attribute &amp;ldquo;data-theme&amp;rdquo; to the body element which you can handle in CSS via attribute selectors, so depending on the theme you have you can update your theme variables.</description></item><item><title>Using NodeJs packages in the browser with import maps</title><link>https://diegosanchezp.github.io/blog/import-maps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://diegosanchezp.github.io/blog/import-maps/</guid><description>What are import maps Import maps is a browser proposal that allow web pages to control the behavior of JavaScript imports, in other words control over what URLs get fetched by JavaScript import statements and import() expressions. A NodeJs developer is used to import packages this way
import { html } from &amp;#39;lit-element&amp;#39;; If we tried to do that directly in the browser it will fail, throwing an error similar to</description></item></channel></rss>